







# **Juan Diego Durango**

# Full Stack Developer JS

### **ABOUT ME**

I am a programmer with extensive experience in developing and maintaining applications and systems. I possess excellent communication, leadership and problem-solving skills. These qualities allow me to work efficiently as a team and meet the quality standards required for each project. I am committed to providing high-value solutions to companies so that they can achieve their desired goals.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# DevGroup, Full Stack Developer

March 2021 - February 2023

- Analysis, development, maintenance and implementation of CMS and ecommerces (B2B, B2C and multilenguage)
- Development of Node services such as loyalty systems, integrations with external systems and customized administrative modules for companies.
- Code analysis and cleaning, optimization, migrations, SEO improvement and implementations with google analytics
- Training to companies and teams on programming
- In charge of leading projects from estimation and costing to deployment and delivery to the client together with a team of people.

Some of the projects I did were: Samsung Pe landings system, Bata Peru, Faces col, among others.

# Sideas, Full Stack Developer

June 2022 - August 2022 / November 2022 - February 2023

- Analysis, development, maintenance and implementation of CMS government and ecommerces
- Development of tracking services in the purchase flow of a customer with their respective analytics system.

## LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native)

English basic

# **EDUCATION HISTORY**

- Software Development Pygmalion, 2017-2021
- FIRST Robotics Competition, 2018-2021
- Software Development Technician, 2020
- Sprint Google Cloud Colombia 2021
- Software Development and Entrepreneurship Fundación Rofé, 2021
- Software engineering Pascual Bravo, 2022
- English LCN Idiomas, 2023 (Currently)

#### **SKILLS**

Javascript

Java

React

Angular

**Typescript** 

NodeJs

Graphql

MongoDB

MySQL